<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="terms">
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>Terms &amp; Conditions:</h1>

        <p>
            KnightRider is intended to assist and enable members of the MGA university community in
            making carpooling arrangements. This program was initiated in response to calls from
            Georgia state agencies and the Board of Regents to take positive measures to save fuel
            and energy costs. Use of this web resource is voluntary and is limited to
            <b><em>faculty, staff and students</em></b> of MGA. Only persons with a valid,
            current MGA  e-mail account will be permitted to register as subscribers to this
            website/app or to post and view postings concerning ride-sharing opportunities.
        </p>

        <p>
            This website provides a means for MGA faculty, staff and students to communicate easily
            regarding ride-sharing and carpooling opportunities based on compatible work and class
            schedules, points of origin, and destinations. <b><em>It is intended for ride-sharing to and
            from work or class and for work-related travel.</em></b> Once a potential participant is
            identified, <b><em>specific arrangements should be handled by direct communication within the
            website/app portal. This website is not intended for ride-sharing arrangements for
            travel not related to employment or enrollment at MGA, which should be made separately.
            </em></b>
        </p>

        <p>
            Employees should understand that <b><em>travel to and from the workplace is generally considered
            not to be within the scope of employment and injuries to persons or property arising while
            going to and from work are not covered by university liability insurance.</em></b> Similarly,
            <b><em>students who share rides to class or elsewhere on campus do so voluntarily and at their
            own risk.</em></b> While state employees are being encouraged to carpool to and from work and to
            shares rides on work-related assignments, and participants will gain personally in terms
            of cost savings, it should be recognized that <b><em>potential damages or injuries incurred due
            to accident or otherwise are not being underwritten or insured by the State of Georgia,
            the Board of Regents, or Middle Georgia State University.</em></b> The risk to an individual
            employee or student who participates in a carpool or other ride-sharing arrangement is
            comparable to the risk he or she would incur when offering or accepting a ride to or from
            a friend for personal travel. Participants should exercise ordinary prudence and satisfy
            themselves that other participating drivers are licensed, competent drivers and that
            vehicles are appropriately insured.
        </p>

        <p>
            MGA will, to the best of its ability, maintain the privacy of information posted on this
            website.app. Users acknowledge that information posted on the site may be viewed by other
            authorized registrants. Users further acknowledge the risk that information posted on the
            site may be viewed by unauthorized users gaining access to authorized accounts. Posting of
            information should be limited to the express purposes of the rideshare program. <b><em>Posting of
            obscene, pornographic or harassing messages is strictly prohibited.</em></b> Concerns about handling
            or content of site postings should be communicated promptly to the webmaster at
            mgaknightriders@mga.edu
        </p>

        <p>
            <b><em>By registering as a user of the MGA Knight Rider Rideshare website/app, each registrant
            agrees to release and hereby releases the Board of Regents, Middle Georgia State University,
            and their officers, employees and agents from any and all liability, damages and costs,
            including attorney's fees, arising from the use of this website/app or participation in
            carpooling or ride-sharing arrangements made in whole or in part through the use of this
            website/app.</em></b>
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>